When murder is just a memory
Out of Thin Air is a documentary, crime film directed by Dylan Howitt.
Set within the stark Icelandic landscape, OUT OF THIN AIR examines the 1976 police
investigation into the disappearance of two men in the early 1970s.
Self, played by Erla Bolladóttir.
Self (archive footage), played by Sævar Ciesiekski.
Self (archive footage), played by Tryggvi Leifsson.
Self (archive footage), played by Albert Skaftason.
Self, played by Guðjón Skarphéðinsson.
Self (archive footage), played by Kristjan Vídarsson.
Out of Thin Air may refer to:
Out of Thin Air, a 2017 documentary about the Guðmundur and Geirfinnur case
Out of Thin Air, the first episode of 2014 documentary The Mystery of Matter
"Out of Thin Air", a song by Howard Jones from Cross
That Line
"Out of Thin Air", a song from the 1996 film Aladdin and the King of Thieves
"Out of Thin Air", an episode of Black Scorpion
Out of Thin Air: The Brief Wonderful Life of Network News, a 1991 memoir by Reuven Frank